Finding Aid for the Reverend Eugene Smathers Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Miscellaneous Series, Boxes Misc. 1-9: Various materials collected by Smathers, arranged by subject. Box Misc. 10: Articles and papers by Smathers, arranged chronologically, 1930-68, plus no dates; Pamphlets by Smathers; publications about Smathers and Big Lick, 1921-68, plus no dates; Board of Na
  - Same (Box Misc. 5, Folder 191)
  - Same (Box Misc. 5, Folder 192)
  - Same (Box Misc. 5, Folder 193)
  - Lectures by E. Smathers - Cumberland Presbyterian Conf., Jan., 1965 (Box Misc. 5, Folder 194)
  - Same - Notes, Interseminary Conf., April, 1956 (Box Misc. 5, Folder 195)
  - Same - Rural Ministers Conference (Box Misc. 5, Folder 196)
  - Same - Rural Ministers School- Bethel College, Aug., 1953 (Box Misc. 5, Folder 197)
  - Legal Matters, Presbyterian, General (Box Misc. 5, Folder 198)
  - Lenten and Easter Sermon Ideas (Box Misc. 5, Folder 199)
  - Lewis and Clark College (Box Misc. 5, Folder 200)
  - Library Books Purchased (Box Misc. 5, Folder 201)
  - Same (Box Misc. 5, Folder 202)
  - Manse Repairs (Box Misc. 5, Folder 203)
  - Map of Big Lick, ca., 1948 (Box Misc. 5, Folder 204)
  - Maps (Box Misc. 5, Folder 205)
  - Maps (Box Misc. 5, Folder 206)
  - Marriage and Parenthood (Box Misc. 5, Folder 207)
  - Marriage and the Home (Holograph Notes) (Box Misc. 5, Folder 208)
  - Material concerning Job Offer of Ass't. Sec. Rural Church Unit (Box Misc. 5, Folder 209)
  - Midcentury White House Conf. on Children and Youth (Box Misc. 5, Folder 210)
  - Mid-South United Presbyterian Ken, June 21-22, 1968 (Box Misc. 5, Folder 211)
  - Ministerial Relations (Box Misc. 5, Folder 211.5)
  - Miscellaneous - by Subject A - Che (Box Misc. 5, Folder 212)
  - Misc.- Chr - Co (Box Misc. 5, Folder 213)
  - Misc.- - D - E (Box Misc. 5, Folder 214)
  - Misc.- F - M (Box Misc. 5, Folder 215)
  - Misc. - N - P (Box Misc. 5, Folder 216)
  - Misc. - Q - W (Box Misc. 5, Folder 217)
  - Mission of the Church, 1957-60 (Box Misc. 5, Folder 218)
  - Missions (Box Misc. 5, Folder 219)
  - Missions, Fortnight of (Box Misc. 5, Folder 220)
  - Missions Information - Oct. Trip to New York (Box Misc. 5, Folder 221)
  - Moderator (Box Misc. 5, Folder 222)
  - Moderator - California Trip, March 23-31, 1968 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 223)
  - Moderator - Engagements Filled and Invitations not accepted (Box Misc. 6, Folder 224)
  - Moderator - General Assembly Program, etc. (Box Misc. 6, Folder 225)
  - Moderator - Itinerary, etc. (Box Misc. 6, Folder 226)
  - Moderator - Itinerary and Reports - General Assembly, 1967 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 227)
  - Moderator - Itinerary and Reports, July-Aug., 1967 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 228)
  - Same, Sept., 1967 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 229)
  - Same, Oct., 1967 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 230)
  - Same, Nov., 1967 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 231)
  - Moderator - Itinerary and Reports, Dec., 1967 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 232)
  - Same, Jan.- March, 1968 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 233)
  - Same, April-May, 1968 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 234)
  - Moderator - Texas Trip, March 14-21, 1968 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 235)
  - Montreat Conference, Aug. 23-24, 1950 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 236)
  - Mountain Migrants 1954-60 (Bibliography of Appalachia) (Box Misc. 6, Folder 237)
  - Natl. Committee on Religion and Rural Life (Box Misc. 6, Folder 238)
  - National Missions (General Material) (Box Misc. 6, Folder 239)
  - Same, including Presbyterian Rural Fellowship Bulletin (Box Misc. 6, Folder 240)
  - National Missions, 1961 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 241)
  - National Missions (as pertains to Cumberland Mtn. Presbytery) *** See folders #91 and #92 also. (Box Misc. 6, Folder 242)
  - National Missions Committee - Cumberland County (Box Misc. 6, Folder 243)
  - National Missions Committee - Presbytery of Cumberland Mtn. (Box Misc. 6, Folder 244)
  - National Presbyterian Health and Welfare Assoc, 1959 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 245)
  - Newsletters (Box Misc. 6, Folder 246)
  - New Testament Theology and the Teachings of Jesus (Box Misc. 6, Folder 247)
  - N.Y. Natl. Missions Promotion Trip, Feb., 1957 - April, 1959 (Box Misc. 6, Folder 248)
  - North Carolina Retreats and Points of Interest (Box Misc. 6, Folder 249)
  - Notebook for Seminars and Survey Workshops (Box Misc. 6, Folder 249.5)
  - Notes - Holograph, Misc. (Box Misc. 6, Folder 250)
  - Notes on Biblical Studies - Holograph (Box Misc. 6, Folder 251)
  - Nutrition (Box Misc. 6, Folder 252)
  - Old Testament (Box Misc. 6, Folder 253)
  - Organ (Box Misc. 6, Folder 254)
  - Ozone Presbyterian Church (Box Misc. 6, Folder 255)
  - Parable of the Prodigal Son - Studies (Box Misc. 6, Folder 256)
  - Parental Education (Box Misc. 6, Folder 257)
  - Pastoral Work (Box Misc. 6, Folder 258)
  - Pastor's Conferences and Miscellaneous Schools (Box Misc. 6, Folder 259)
  - Same (Box Misc. 6, Folder 260)
  - Same (Box Misc. 6, Folder 261)
  - Pastor's Life and Work (Box Misc. 6, Folder 262)
  - Pavilion (Box Misc. 6, Folder 263)
  - Personal Papers - Smathers (Box Misc. 6, Folder 264)
  - Philosophy of Rural Life (Box Misc. 6, Folder 265)
  - Photographs (Also see two photographs - Blue Ridge Staff 1928, and Presbyterian Theological Seminary, Faculty & Class, 1932 - Louisvill. (Box Misc. 7, Folder 266)
  - Playa Ky. in BOX #22 - Pamphlets) (Box Misc. 7, Folder 267)
  - Political Science (Box Misc. 7, Folder 268)
  - Population (Box Misc. 7, Folder 269)
  - Presbyterian Church - Miscellaneous Information (Box Misc. 7, Folder 270)
  - Presbyterian Churches in Tennessee (Box Misc. 7, Folder 271)
  - Same (Box Misc. 7, Folder 272)
  - Presbyterian Rural Fellowship, 1958 (Box Misc. 7, Folder 273)
  - Same - Executive Committee (Box Misc. 7, Folder 274)
  - Same - New York Meeting, Oct., 1958 (Box Misc. 7, Folder 275)
  - Same - York, Pa. Meeting, Oct., 1958 (Box Misc. 7, Folder 276)
  - Presbyterian Summer Conferences (Box Misc. 7, Folder 277)
  - Printed Circulars (Box Misc. 7, Folder 278)
  - Program Materials for Young People (Box Misc. 7, Folder 279)
  - Prophets (Box Misc. 7, Folder 280)
  - Psychology and Religion - Smathers’ Seminary Notes (Box Misc. 7, Folder 281)
  - P.T.A. (Box Misc. 7, Folder 282)
  - Public Health (Box Misc. 7, Folder 283)
  - Public Welfare (Box Misc. 7, Folder 284)
  - Public Worship (Box Misc. 7, Folder 285)
  - Race Relations (Box Misc. 7, Folder 286)
  - Reading Motes A - B (Arranged by author's last name) (Box Misc. 7, Folder 287)
  - Same C - D (Box Misc. 7, Folder 288)
  - Same E - G (Box Misc. 7, Folder 289)
  - Same H - J (Box Misc. 7, Folder 290)
  - Same K - L (Box Misc. 7, Folder 291)
  - Same M - N (Box Misc. 7, Folder 292)
  - Same O - P (Box Misc. 7, Folder 293)
  - Same R - S (Box Misc. 7, Folder 294)
  - Same T - V (Box Misc. 7, Folder 295)
  - Same w - Z (Box Misc. 7, Folder 296)
  - Reading Notes - Notebooks (Box Misc. 7, Folder 297)
  - Reading Notes on Books (Box Misc. 7, Folder 298)
  - Religion, General, Religion in the Home, and Roman Catholic Issues (Box Misc. 7, Folder 299)
  - Reports of Historical Significance (Box Misc. 7, Folder 300)
  - Revelation, Book of (Box Misc. 7, Folder 301)
  - Rototiller (Box Misc. 7, Folder 302)
  - Rural - Christian Agriculture (Box Misc. 7, Folder 303)
  - Rural - Christian Agriculture (Box Misc. 7, Folder 304)
  - Rural Church (Box Misc. 7, Folder 305)
  - Same (Box Misc. 7, Folder 306)
  - Rural Church and Family Farm Pamphlet - Outline (Box Misc. 7, Folder 307)
  - Rural Church Commission - Conf. of Southern Mtn. Workers, 1940 (Box Misc. 7, Folder 308)
  - Rural Church Commission - Tenn. Council of Churches (Box Misc. 7, Folder 309)
  - Rural Community Conf., 1935-41 (Box Misc. 7, Folder 310)
  - Rural Housing (Box Misc. 7, Folder 311)
  - Rural Life and Rural Life Association (Box Misc. 7, Folder 312)
  - Rural Life and Agriculture (Box Misc. 7, Folder 313)
  - Rural Life - Bibliographies and Statements on Rural Life (Box Misc. 8, Folder 314)
  - Rural Life - Bio-Dynamic Farming (Box Misc. 8, Folder 315)
  - Same - Christian Education (Box Misc. 8, Folder 316)
  - Same - Church and Land (Box Misc. 8, Folder 317)
  - Same - The Church and Rural America - Class Notes (Box Misc. 8, Folder 318)
  - Same - The Church and Rural Youth (Box Misc. 8, Folder 319)
  - Same - Church Farm Conditions (Box Misc. 8, Folder 320)
  - Same - Cooperatives (Box Misc. 8, Folder 321)
  - Same - The Family (Box Misc. 8, Folder 322)
  - Same - The Family (Box Misc. 8, Folder 323)
  - Same - Land (Box Misc. 8, Folder 324)
  - Same - Organizations (Box Misc. 8, Folder 325)
  - Same - Plans and Programs (Box Misc. 8, Folder 326)
  - Rural Life - Rural Church (Box Misc. 8, Folder 327)
  - Same - Rural Church and its Community (Box Misc. 8, Folder 328)
  - Same - Rural Church and its Community (Box Misc. 8, Folder 329)
  - Same - The Rural Community, Its Organization and Agencies (Box Misc. 8, Folder 330)
  - Same - The Rural Community, Its Organization and Agencies (Box Misc. 8, Folder 331)
  - Rural Life - The Rural Family and the Church (Box Misc. 8, Folder 332)
  - Same (Box Misc. 8, Folder 333)
  - Rural Life - Rural Field, Home Missions (Box Misc. 8, Folder 334)
  - Same - Rural Minister (Box Misc. 8, Folder 335)
  - Same - The Rural Missionary Program at Home (Box Misc. 8, Folder 336)
  - Same - Scarritt College Workshop for Rural Workers, 1944 (Box Misc. 8, Folder 337)
  - Same - Seminar in Rural Life (Box Misc. 8, Folder 338)
  - Rural Missions (Box Misc. 8, Folder 339)
  - Sacraments (Box Misc. 8, Folder 340)
  - Scrapbook of Jr. High Girls, Pine Street Presby. Church. (Box Misc. 8, Folder 341)
  - Scrapbook, "The Once-in-a-While Book" (Box Misc. 8, Folder 342)
  - Scrapbook, "The Once-in-a-While Book" No. 2 (Sermon Suggestions) (Box Misc. 8, Folder 343)
  - Social Action (Box Misc. 8, Folder 344)
  - Social Science, The Henry George School of (Box Misc. 8, Folder 345)
  - Social Work (Box Misc. 8, Folder 346)
  - Socialism (Box Misc. 8, Folder 347)
  - Sociology - General (Box Misc. 8, Folder 348)
  - Source Materials for Courses (Box Misc. 8, Folder 349)
  - Same (Box Misc. 8, Folder 350)
  - Same (Box Misc. 8, Folder 351)
  - Southeastern Cooperator, 1940-41 (Box Misc. 8, Folder 352)
  - Same, 1942-43 (Box Misc. 8, Folder 353)
  - Southern Mtns. Migration Conf, 1961-66 (Box Misc. 9, Folder 354)
  - Southern Rural Life Council (Box Misc. 9, Folder 355)
  - Southern Rural Life Council (Box Misc. 9, Folder 356)
  - Southern Rural Life Council - Report, etc. (Box Misc. 9, Folder 357)
  - Speeches and Articles by Others (Box Misc. 9, Folder 358)
  - Summer School, Maryville, 1951 (Box Misc. 9, Folder 359)
  - Summer Students, 1962, and Work Camp, 1963 (Box Misc. 9, Folder 360)
  - Sunday School Lesson - Used, Oct., 1953-1955 (Box Misc. 9, Folder 361)
  - Synod of Kentucky (Box Misc. 9, Folder 362)
  - Synod of Mid-South (Box Misc. 9, Folder 362.5)
  - Synod of Oklahoma, June 17-20, 1946 (Box Misc. 9, Folder 363)
  - Talks - Louisville Seminary, Alumni Luncheon Rural Pastor's Conf. (Box Misc. 9, Folder 364)
  - Teaching Notes and Syllabi for Smathers' Courses (Box Misc. 9, Folder 365)
  - Teaching Religion (Box Misc. 9, Folder 366)
  - Theology - Smathers' Seminary Notes (Box Misc. 9, Folder 367)
  - Title III - E.S.E.A.- Cumberland County, 1966 (Box Misc. 9, Folder 368)
  - Transportation Information (Box Misc. 9, Folder 369)
  - T.V.A. (Box Misc. 9, Folder 370)
  - United Presbyterian Church, U.S.A. - Bd. of Christian Education (Box Misc. 9, Folder 371)
  - Same (Box Misc. 9, Folder 372)
  - Same (Box Misc. 9, Folder 373)
  - United Presbyterian Church, U.S.A.- General Council (Box Misc. 9, Folder 374)
  - Same (Box Misc. 9, Folder 375)
  - Same + Miscellaneous (Box Misc. 9, Folder 376)
  - Univ. of Georgia Religion in Life Week, Feb., 10-14, 1957 (Box Misc. 9, Folder 377)
  - Uplands Board (Box Misc. 9, Folder 378)
  - Uplands Cumberland Medical Center (Box Misc. 9, Folder 379)
  - Vacation Schools: Places, Materials, Records (Box Misc. 9, Folder 380)
  - Vanderbilt Courses (Box Misc. 9, Folder 381)
  - Viet Nam (including topical notes from Michael to Eugene Smathers) (Box Misc. 9, Folder 382)
  - Visual Aids: Descriptions and Scripts (Box Misc. 9, Folder 383)
  - Same - and posters (Box Misc. 9, Folder 384)
  - Westfield, N.J. (Box Misc. 9, Folder 385)
  - We Will (Box Misc. 9, Folder 386)
  - Wilson, Warren H. (Box Misc. 9, Folder 387)
  - Warren H. Wilson House of Health (Box Misc. 9, Folder 388)
  - Work Camp and Student Visits, 1954-57 (Box Misc. 9, Folder 389)
  - Worship (Box Misc. 9, Folder 390)
  - Worship, Aids to (Box Misc. 9, Folder 391)
  - Worship Materials (Box Misc. 9, Folder 392)
  - Worship - Plans and Suggestions for Morning Worship (Box Misc. 9, Folder 393)
  - Worship Service Bulletins (Box Misc. 9, Folder 394)
  - Youth Fellowship (Box Misc. 9, Folder 395)
  - Youth Groups and Summer Students (Box Misc. 9, Folder 396)
  - Youth Groups, Workcamps, 1960-61 (Box Misc. 9, Folder 397)
  - Yowell, Dorothy - Monthly Report, Rural Church Work in Health, 1948-52 (Box Misc. 9, Folder 398)
  - Articles and Papers by Smathers Arranged Chronologically, 1930-32, plus a listing of Smathers' publications by P. Smathers Konstam. (Box Misc. 10, Folder 1)
  - Articles and Papers by Smathers, 1932-1939 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 2)
  - Same, 1940-1942 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 3)
  - Same, 1943 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 4)
  - Same, 1943 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 5)
  - Same, 1944 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 6)
  - Same, 1945 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 7)
  - Same, 1946 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 8)
  - Same, 1946 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 9)
  - Same, 1947 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 10)
  - Same, 1948-1949 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 11)
  - Same, 1950-1954 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 12)
  - Same, 1955-64 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 13)
  - Same, 1965-68 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 14)
  - Same, no dates (Box Misc. 10, Folder 15)
  - Pamphlets by Smathers (A Primer for Friends of Soil, Stewards of the, Soil, etc.) (Box Misc. 10, Folder 16)
  - Publications about Smathers and Big Lick - 1921-1943, plus a guide by P.S. Konstam (Box Misc. 10, Folder 17)
  - Publications about Smathers and Big Lick, 1944-1946 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 18)
  - Same, 1947-1950 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 19)
  - Same, 1952-1965 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 20)
  - Same, May, 1967-June 15, 1967 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 21)
  - Same, June 15, 1967-July, 1967 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 22)
  - Same, August, 1967-December, 1967 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 23)
  - Same - March, 1968-October, 1968 & no dates (Box Misc. 10, Folder 24)
  - Board of Natl. Missions - Monthly Reports by Smathers, 1932-1934 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 25)
  - Same, 1935, 1937-1940 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 26)
  - Same, 1941-1947 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 27)
  - Same, 1953-1954, 1957, 1959-1963 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 28)
  - Same - 1964-1968 + Miscellaneous Reports by Smathers (Box Misc. 10, Folder 29)
  - Board of Natl. Missions - Monthly Reports by Others, 1944 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 30)
  - Same, 1945 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 31)
  - Same, 1948 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 32)
  - Same, 1949 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 33)
  - Same, 1949 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 34)
  - Same, 1950 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 35)
  - Same, 1953-54 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 36)
  - Same, 1954 (Box Misc. 10, Folder 37)
  - Board of Natl. Missions - Monthly Reports by Others, 1955 (Box Misc. 11, Folder 38)
  - Same, 1956 (Box Misc. 11, Folder 39)
  - Same, 1957 (Box Misc. 11, Folder 40)
  - Same, 1958 (Box Misc. 11, Folder 41)
  - Same, 1959 (Box Misc. 11, Folder 42)
  - Board of Natl. Missions - Monthly Reports by Others, 1960 (Box Misc. 11, Folder 43)
  - Same, 1961 (Box Misc. 11, Folder 44)
  - Same, 1962 (Box Misc. 11, Folder 45)
  - Same, 1963 (Box Misc. 11, Folder 46)
  - Same - 1965, 1967-1968, and no dates (Box Misc. 11, Folder 47)
  - Board of Natl. Missions - Reports on Various Projects, and Miscellaneous Reports (By Others) (Box Misc. 11, Folder 48)
    Also in Box #11, begin separate series numbered 11-1, 11-2, etc. of pamphlets collected by Smathers, arranged by publisher.
  - Abingdon-Cokesbury Press (Box Misc. 11, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Extension Service - Cumberland County, Tenn. (Box Misc. 11, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Missions, Inc. (Box Misc. 11, Folder 3)
  - The American Association for Adult Education (Box Misc. 11, Folder 4)
  - American Baptist Home Mission Society (Box Misc. 11, Folder 5)
  - American Bible Society (Box Misc. 11, Folder 6)
  - American Bible Society (Box Misc. 11, Folder 7)
  - American Bible Society (Box Misc. 11, Folder 8)
  - American Birth Control League (Box Misc. 11, Folder 9)
  - American Board of Missions to the Jews (Box Misc. 11, Folder 10)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box Misc. 11, Folder 11)
  - American Council on Education (Box Misc. 11, Folder 12)
  - American Country Life Association (Box Misc. 11, Folder 13)
  - American Forest Products Industries (Box Misc. 11, Folder 14)
  - American Friends Service Committee (Box Misc. 11, Folder 15)
  - American Humane Education Society (Box Misc. 11, Folder 16)
  - The American Institute of Cooperation (Box Misc. 11, Folder 17)
  - American Institute of Family Relations (Box Misc. 11, Folder 18)
  - American Library Association (Box Misc. 11, Folder 19)
  - American National Red Cross (Box Misc. 11, Folder 20)
  - American Potash Institute (Box Misc. 11, Folder 21)
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith (Box Misc. 11, Folder 22)
  - Arkansas Agricultural Experiment Station (Box Misc. 11, Folder 23)
  - Army Orientation Branch (Box Misc. 11, Folder 24)
  - Asheville Farm School Press (Box Misc. 11, Folder 25)
  - A Miscellaneous Ad - American Cancer Society (Box Misc. 11, Folder 26)
  - A Misc. A.F.L. - Annals (Box Misc. 11, Folder 27)
  - A Misc. Ap - At (Box Misc. 11, Folder 28)
  - Belsaw Machinery Co. (Box Misc. 11, Folder 29)
  - B Miscellaneous (Box Misc. 11, Folder 30)
  - Calvary Church (Box Misc. 12, Folder 1)
  - Chicago, University of (Box Misc. 12, Folder 2)
  - Christianity and Modern Man, 1950-1951 (Box Misc. 12, Folder 3)
  - Christianity and Modern Man, 1955 (Box Misc. 12, Folder 4)
  - Christianity and Modern Man, 1956, 1965 (Box Misc. 12, Folder 5)
  - Christian Rural Fellowship (Box Misc. 12, Folder 6)
  - Churches of Christ in America, The Federal Council of the, n.d.'s and 1932-40 (Box Misc. 12, Folder 7)
  - Same, 1940-1944 (Box Misc. 12, Folder 8)
  - Same, 1945-1946 (Box Misc. 12, Folder 9)
  - Same, 1947-1950 (Box Misc. 12, Folder 10)
  - Churches of Christ in America, National Council of the, 1955-1960 (Box Misc. 12, Folder 11)
  - Same, 1961-1967 (Box Misc. 12, Folder 12)
  - Church of the Brethen (Box Misc. 12, Folder 13)
  - Columbia University (Box Misc. 12, Folder 14)
  - Commission on Interracial Cooperation (Box Misc. 12, Folder 15)
  - "Committee of 100" (Box Misc. 12, Folder 16)
  - The Common Council for American Unity (Box Misc. 12, Folder 17)
  - Community Service Committee (Box Misc. 12, Folder 18)
  - Community Service, Inc. (Box Misc. 12, Folder 19)
  - Conference of Southern Mtn. Workers (Box Misc. 12, Folder 20)
  - Congregational and Christian Churches (Box Misc. 12, Folder 21)
  - Congregational and Christian Churches (Box Misc. 12, Folder 22)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations (Box Misc. 12, Folder 23)
  - The Cooperative League of the U.S.A. (Box Misc. 12, Folder 24)
  - Cooperative Recreation Service (Box Misc. 12, Folder 25)
  - Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station (Box Misc. 12, Folder 26)
  - Council for Democracy (Box Misc. 12, Folder 27)
  - Council of the Southern Mtns. (Box Misc. 12, Folder 28)
  - Cumberland County Churches of Christ (The Lord's Way) (Box Misc. 12, Folder 29)
  - Cumberland Farmers Cooperative (Box Misc. 12, Folder 30)
  - "C" Miscellaneous Ca - Chicago (Box Misc. 12, Folder 31)
  - "C" Miscellaneous Child - Civilian (Box Misc. 12, Folder 32)
  - "C" Miscellaneous Commission - Congress (Box Misc. 13, Folder 1)
  - "C" Miscellaneous Consumer's Culpepper (Box Misc. 13, Folder 2)
  - "C" Miscellaneous Cumberland Curtis (Box Misc. 13, Folder 3)
  - Drew Theological Seminary, Dept. of the Rural Church (Box Misc. 13, Folder 4)
  - "D" Miscellaneous (Box Misc. 13, Folder 5)
  - Eldridge Entertainment House (Box Misc. 13, Folder 6)
  - "E" Miscellaneous (Box Misc. 13, Folder 7)
  - Farmers Federation (Box Misc. 13, Folder 8)
  - Farm Foundation (Box Misc. 13, Folder 9)
  - Farm Foundation (Box Misc. 13, Folder 10)
  - Federal Works Agency (Box Misc. 13, Folder 11)
  - The Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box Misc. 13, Folder 12)
  - Fellowship of Southern Churchmen (Box Misc. 13, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America (Box Misc. 13, Folder 14)
  - The Foreign Policy Association (Box Misc. 13, Folder 15)
  - Fort Valley State College (Box Misc. 13, Folder 16)
  - French, Samuel (Box Misc. 13, Folder 17)
  - Friendship Press (Box Misc. 13, Folder 18)
  - Friends of Democracy (Box Misc. 13, Folder 19)
  - Friends of the Land (Box Misc. 13, Folder 20)
  - "F" Miscellaneous Fa - Fels (Box Misc. 13, Folder 21)
  - "F" Misc. Felt - Fi (Box Misc. 13, Folder 22)
  - "F" Misc. Fl - Fu (Box Misc. 13, Folder 23)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs (Box Misc. 13, Folder 24)
  - General Mills, Inc. (Box Misc. 13, Folder 25)
  - General Motors (Box Misc. 13, Folder 26)
  - "G" Miscellaneous (Box Misc. 13, Folder 27)
  - "Have-More" Plan (Box Misc. 13, Folder 28)
  - The Home Missions Council of North America (Box Misc. 14, Folder 1)
  - The Home Missions Council of North America (Box Misc. 14, Folder 2)
  - "H" Miscellaneous (Box Misc. 14, Folder 3)
  - Illinois Council of Churches (Box Misc. 14, Folder 4)
  - Illinois, University of (Box Misc. 14, Folder 5)
  - Indiana Council of Churches (Box Misc. 14, Folder 6)
  - International Council of Religious Education (Box Misc. 14, Folder 7)
  - The International Council of Religious Education (Box Misc. 14, Folder 8)
  - International Harvester Co. (Box Misc. 14, Folder 9)
  - Iowa State College (Box Misc. 14, Folder 10)
  - "I" Miscellaneous (Ind. - Inter-Religious) (Box Misc. 14, Folder 11)
  - "J" Miscellaneous (Box Misc. 14, Folder 12)
  - Kentucky Agricultural Experiment Station, 1930 - June, 1947 (Box Misc. 14, Folder 13)
  - Same, Aug., 17 - 1953 (Box Misc. 14, Folder 14)
  - Knowlton, D.B. & Co. (Box Misc. 14, Folder 15)
  - "K" Miscellaneous (Box Misc. 14, Folder 16)
  - Legaue for Industrial Democracy (Box Misc. 14, Folder 17)
  - League for Industrial Democracy (Box Misc. 14, Folder 18)
  - Lindstrom, David Edgar (Box Misc. 14, Folder 19)
  - Louisiana State University (Box Misc. 14, Folder 20)
  - Louisville Presbyterian Seminary (Box Misc. 14, Folder 21)
  - Lutheran Church (Box Misc. 14, Folder 22)
  - "L" Miscellaneous (Box Misc. 14, Folder 23)
  - Maryland Agricultural Experiment Station (Box Misc. 14, Folder 24)
  - Massachusetts State College (Box Misc. 14, Folder 25)
  - Same (Box Misc. 14, Folder 26)
  - Methodist Church (Box Misc. 14, Folder 27)
  - Methodist Church (Box Misc. 15, Folder 1)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church, South (Box Misc. 15, Folder 2)
  - Methodist Publishing House and Methodist Book Concern (Box Misc. 15, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. (Box Misc. 15, Folder 4)
  - Michigan Agricultural Experiment Station (Box Misc. 15, Folder 5)
  - Minnesota -Agricultural Experiment Station, Agricultural Extension Service, - Dept. of Education (Box Misc. 15, Folder 6)
  - Mississippi State College (Extension Service) (Box Misc. 15, Folder 7)
  - Missouri Agricultural Experiment Station (Box Misc. 15, Folder 8)
  - "M" Miscellaneous (Box Misc. 15, Folder 9)
  - Natl.Assoc.for the Advancement of Colored People (R.A.A.C.P.) (Box Misc. 15, Folder 10)
  - National Assoc. of Manufacturers (Box Misc. 15, Folder 11)
  - Same (Box Misc. 15, Folder 12)
  - The National Assoc. of Soil Conservation Districts (Box Misc. 15, Folder 13)
  - National Catholic Rural Life Conference (Box Misc. 15, Folder 14)